Downloaded @ subs4free.club
- You all through?
- Almost.
Found one more in here.
- Bag it up.
You ever seen
anything like this?
- No.
Not so close to home.
Also, when bagging
the last body,
the female?
I found this.
Agent Lerner?
It gets weirder.
I think this one left a
message written in blood.
I think they were
plugged before burning.
Joe.
Joe?
- Jovan.
- Make sure you
stay hydrated, Miss Kamen.
- Where am I?
- It's recommended
for someone in your state.
- My state?
What happened?
- I think it's time you
answered my questions.
- Can you
tell me what's going on?
- What's going on?
Dingy decor, me,
full uniform, armed,
cheap-ass coffee at four
in the fucking morning.
I don't know, Miss Kamen,
maybe it's a police station.
You looking for these?
We call this the evidence.
We'll keep the Xanax for now.
- Why am I in a police station?
- We've been through
this Miss Kamen,
but somehow I just knew
you wouldn't remember it.
- Would you please
tell me what happened?
- Let's look, hm?
Two in the morning.
Patrol finds you passed out
behind the wheel of your own car
in the center divider,
completely out of it.
Let's just say your
toxicology report
did not come back great.
- Look, if, if,
if there is a fine
or a ticket or something,
I can just-
- I think it's a little bit
more serious than that.
You could do real time for this.
So why don't you
walk me through it.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
- Hey, sorry, am I
interrupting the date?
- Um, no,
uh, not at all, um.
I, uh, I was on my way
and I kind of
bee-lined for a bar.
I guess I needed
a, a little more alone time.
- Alone time?
Your whole life is alone time
unless you're hanging out
with Brandon and me.
- So you told me
about Sarah James before.
Was she at the bar with you?
- No, I was on the phone
with her from the bar.
- You go there often?
- I wouldn't say often.
They have a nice wine list.
- I bet they do.
You know, in my experience,
I find it's the winos
who get the DUIs.
Do you find that to be true?
- I don't have a history of DUI.
Can I use the restroom?
- No.
- I really need to.
Miss Kamen?
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Glad you're up and about.
- How may I direct your call?
- Excuse the, uh, the precinct.
We're doing major renovations.
Donut?
I aim for variety.
Come on. Don't be shy.
They're good.
- Thank you.
- Mm.
Of course.
Strawberry, huh?
I'm more of a matcha glaze guy.
I love this place.
Hm, Detective Avery.
We met earlier, but you
weren't doing too good.
Hm.
You ready to talk?
- Where's the other detective?
- She's with a witness that
I picked up this morning.
Friend of yours, I believe.
Come on, can leave that here.
- So
do I start talking?
- Can you state your
full name for the record?
- Robert Edward Audrey.
- And date
of birth, please?
- That would
be April 20th, 1987.
- Is this sort of
what you do, Mr. Audrey?
You take strange
women home with you?
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Albert. Who's the new guy?
- I just know he's
drinking bourbon.
- Okay, so, so let's
make the next one
a Halitz 18.
- Got it.
- That's a classy drink.
- I'm a, I'm a classy
lady.
- She was a little older,
but I figured, why not?
We got in her car,
went for a little drive.
She liked how that went.
She wanted to take
me home with her.
She was bombed.
Tried to take her keys
from her, but, you know,
can't tell women nothing.
And that was it.
She took off, man.
She took off near the fucking
train tracks or whatever.
- Train tracks?
- Yeah, train tracks.
You know, choo choo? Beep beep?
I don't know what the
fuck else sound they make.
- Thank you.
- I don't remember any of that.
- Hm.
- And I- I wasn't drunk.
- It's not the way
Mr. Audrey tells it.
And the bartender did
corroborate his story.
- You talked to Albert?
- Jesus. You know
the bartender's name?
- I don't know this guy.
What if he drugged me?
- Wait, he roofied you
so that he could almost
get killed in your car?
- I'm not sure what
happened, okay,
but I feel, I feel fine.
Can I please just pay
the ticket and go home?
- Detective Moon, you,
you didn't tell her?
- I was waiting to see
how things developed.
- Tell me what?
- Pretty nasty damage to
the front of your car.
- Yeah, there was, there
was quite a bit of blood.
- Like you hit
somebody with your car.
- Miss Kamen? Let's go.
Renovation crew is
using the women's cell,
so this is all we got.
- Don't
worry about Sully.
He's harmless and she's
just a scared rich girl.
Let us know when
you're ready to talk.
- Hello?
Hello?
- Sarah?
- May I help you?
- Hi, uh, I
had a.
- Yeah, I'm
Detective Moon.
- She, uh, talked-
Can I see her? I
brought her some things.
- Of course.
- You got one minute.
- I don't understand.
Why are you here?
- Listen.
Are you okay?
- No.
I may have been
involved in an accident.
Where's Brandon?
- He's with my neighbor.
- Detective Moon.
Yeah, it's my dad. Is he okay?
- Miss James. Thank
you for coming.
We'll be in touch.
Skip breakfast this morning?
- Hello?
Hello?
That son of a bitch came to me.
He didn't know what was up.
Oh, that
old bastard knows now.
He knows now.
- Detective!
- They found somebody.
A cyclist, close to
where they found you.
It's not looking so good.
Do you have anything
to say about that?
- May I have my pills?
- I don't think so. No.
Hold on to these until you're
a little more cooperative.
- Let's say that I was drugged,
then how can I be
held accountable?
- You came in and we
got a urine sample.
Do you remember that?
- No, I don't remember.
And it was, it was
something else.
Could it have been?
Oh, Duckhorn Cabernet.
Drank the whole bottle.
Goddamn.
For what you paid for it,
I'd have drank the
whole bottle too.
- I didn't, I drank that
over the whole night.
- Lady!
- I was perfectly fine.
- Then why is that
cyclist's blood
all over your fucking bumper?
- Okay, all right, all right.
All right, let's.
Okay, look, if you just tell us
everything that happened,
this will go a lot smoother.
- Hit and run.
It's a light penalty.
- It's light.
- Or harsh.
- Can be. It's really up to you.
- I have some really,
really good news.
So, the adoption is
finally official.
- Oh my gosh.
That's, uh, that's great news.
I'm, I'm really happy for you.
- Miss Kamen, you okay?
- I tried to take her keys
from her, but, you know,
you can't tell women nothing.
- I don't remember any of that.
I'd like to speak to a lawyer.
- 45 minutes.
- Fuck!
- I called it!
- Fucker!
What are you? A
goddamn clairvoyant?
I gave her 15 minutes max.
- You know what, she put a
valiant effort in though.
Right? Then she had to sweep
everything under the rug.
Once you get a lawyer,
for better or for
worse, it's happening.
Isn't that right, Miss Kamen?
Miss Kamen?
Your attorney is here
to have a word with you.
- Um, this is not my lawyer.
- Isaac Barsi with Rosenberg,
Swinson and Velasquez.
I came as soon as I could.
Uh, Mrs. Rosenberg had a
family vacation on the books
for several months now,
she must have mentioned it.
- No, she didn't.
- She's currently
in Tokyo with her sister.
- Can you call her?
- We've left word for
her to call us back
as soon as she wakes up.
I can assure, you're
in good hands.
- All right.
I've got the photos of the
damage done to your car.
No immediate information
on what the cause of it was,
but we'll get to
the bottom of it.
- You still don't remember
how this happened?
- My client maintains,
she has no memory of
the last several hours.
- That's a
little convenient.
- Maybe for you it is.
Gives you a nice blank canvas
for you to paint
your own narrative.
- Look, we have witnesses.
- Who? You mean the
guy from the bar?
- You
think his testimony
would hold up against my client
who is a pillar
of this community?
Her record is spotless.
- She has no record.
- All you have is the car,
assuming the blood even
matches that of the victim
and that you people haven't
already managed to botch the...
- Chain of custody.
- Chain of custody on the DNA.
- So where is my car right now?
- Forensics.
- Impound lot.
- Forensics is going over
it at the impound lot.
- Can't you get forensics
to check the DNA?
I- I could have hit
a deer or something.
- I was, I was just
gonna suggest that.
- So shouldn't you check on it?
- Yeah, of, of course,
Miss Kamen, um,
I'll get that all settled.
That all sorted out for you.
Oh, uh, can the girl at the
front validate my parking?
- I mean, you could
just bill me for it.
- I'll walk you out.
- Can I please stay
here at this time?
- Oh, you'll be all right.
Look, if Sully starts
spouting out limericks,
give me a holler then.
That means his
blood's about to boil.
- Bloody hell,
can't come up this way.
Closer, a little bit.
- Officer.
- Ain't no cops around.
- You gotta let me outta here.
- I don't see this.
- This guy's insane.
- Sit down.
- Listen to him.
- You y'all can
step up this way.
- Listen to him.
- Hey, be real careful!
- He doesn't even
say real words.
- Be real careful of them
wires and them towers.
- I got parents.
- Ain't no cops around.
I don't care.
- Rich ones,
with real lawyers,
and they'll sue you.
- Really?
Sully!
- There once was a
fisherman named Fisher.
- Sully, no!
Sully! What the?
Gun!
Shoot him!
Shoot!
Shoot, shoot!
Shoot him!
- Lisa!
Lisa!
You okay? You okay?
Stay.
Breathe. Breathe.
It's okay. It's okay.
Come on. Come on, come on!
Stay with me. Stay with me.
I gotta call this in.
- I was trying to help.
- You shot a fucking cop!
- I didn't mean to.
- I don't wanna hear
your mouth right now.
- Okay, it was
your partner, she-
- Don't you dare talk
about Detective Moon.
- He was strangling her.
- Listen.
- Okay,
and he was going
crazy, I didn't.
- I don't wanna
know your thoughts.
I want you to sit
down and shut up.
- I'm not gonna
get blamed for this!
- What'd you say?
- I'm gonna get blamed
for this.
- You're worried
about getting blamed?
You just shot a fucking cop.
A human being.
That's mandatory life in
prison without parole.
That's what you
need to worry about.
- $1 million.
- What?
- To make all this go away.
- I must look stupid to
you or something, huh?
I'm supposed to believe
that you are sitting
on that kind of cash.
- I'll transfer it
to you right now.
I'll just disappear.
- Hm.
You're a piece of work.
- 1.2!
That's gotta be more than
10 times you make in a year.
- Two million.
- 1.5.
That is all I have, hand to God.
- You must have some nasty
shit in that closet, lady.
You got one minute.
Log into your account.
I'll be right back.
- Hello?
This is Tiffany.
Just one moment, please.
Hello.
This is Tiffany.
How may I direct your call?
- Miss, Miss Kamen.
What, what, what
are you doing here?
I actually just spoke to the lab
regarding the test
results on the car and-
- Mr. Barsi.
- I just need to
speak to my client
regarding the test results.
- What are you doing at my desk?
Huh?
- I just need to speak
to her regarding-
- You need to leave.
- And I-
- You need to go?
- No, I- I'm her attorney.
- You need to go.
- No, no.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Miss Kamen!
Apologize for the outburst.
It's just
attorney-client meetings
need to be approved
in advance before.
What the hell are you doing?
- It took me a minute to see it.
- See what? What, we had a deal.
- I don't deal with
bullshit artists.
- Okay, look,
I didn't think you could
make a worse mistake
than what you've already done,
but pulling a gun out
on a cop, that's worse.
- It would be if you were a cop.
- Counselor.
Your client is
making a big mistake.
I think you need to
step in and counsel her.
- Uh, Miss Kamen,
as your attorney,
I strongly advise
you to surrender.
- This is fake.
The bathrooms, the phones,
even the badges are fake.
Look.
- Prop Department.
- Miss Kamen,
this used to be the
Property Crimes Division.
We're under
renovations, I told you.
- You let me go and
nobody gets hurt.
- I'm sorry Miss Kamen,
but I can't do that.
- Miss Kamen, I- I've
known Detective Avery
for a long time.
He can be trusted.
Please, please, just
put the gun down.
- So your friend Sarah,
she's in on it too?
Your attorney?
Miss Kamen.
No, no, wait! No, no, no!
Shit.
I don't know what
you were thinking.
- What do you
mean? She made you.
She figured it out.
- I would've
recovered from this.
I do this for a living, I...
- I'm, look, I'm so.
Fuck.
- She'll be up soon.
- Then we
go to work, baby.
- Yeah, we do.
- Anything?
- Still out.
- Look, I'm sorry, man.
I thought I was being proactive.
I mean, like, what if she had
the gun with the real rounds?
- What the fuck are you doing
pointing that thing at me?
- Sorry.
- Where did we discuss
the live gun would be?
- In the, in the, in the...
- Locked up in the desk, right?
Where was the gun?
- Locked in the, in the-
- Exactly.
We're professionals.
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's act like it.
- I'm sorry, I- I forgot.
- All right, folks,
we got three hours
to get this whole
thing done, okay?
So we gotta chop chop.
Let's get this thing going.
And keep that
motherfucker away from me.
He's lucky I didn't bash
his fucking head in.
He was walking around here
like he was on a
goddamn coffee break.
- I talked to Isaac.
It's all good.
- Well,
you brought him in.
So he's your responsibility.
- He came through
when it mattered.
You did good for
your first sham.
- All right, love birds.
We're going to plan B.
- Plan B?
- Plan B, baby.
That's you and me.
All right, kid,
get me some coffee.
- Ready for
a little QandA, huh?
All right.
- Let's go.
- What's he doing, baby?
- Our time, baby.
- Woo.
Let's go.
- Oh, and Sully.
Start off slow.
Work your way up to
the rough stuff, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- We got this.
- Okay?
Robert, go grab her
and bring her in the
interrogation room.
Oh, Jesus.
- You okay, baby?
- Yeah.
Coffee's actually
cutting the Jones,
but my hands are
fucking dancing.
- Who are you?
- A friend of Louis Denton's.
Nah, fuck that.
He was more like my brother.
We were a couple of
foster system rejects.
We grew up.
He started his business
and I started mine.
- I don't know who
you think I am.
- I know.
You're the consultant, right?
The consultant.
He told me about all
those late night meetings
you guys used to
have in his office.
On top of his desk.
All night.
He also told me about that, uh.
What is it? A birthmark?
- Oh, it's, um, it's like
a, like a fancy goose.
- Ah. A fancy goose.
May I?
I just. I wanna see it.
Hm.
Mm.
Oh, there it is.
Oh. Oh.
That's fancy.
Let's cut the bullshit.
No more early retirement.
- Okay.
Yeah, I knew him.
- We've established that.
- I didn't know he was married.
And I'm sorry for
what happened to him.
- Did you kill him?
I mean, not that it
matters at this point,
but I'd like to know.
- No.
I didn't kill him.
I loved him.
- Maybe you did.
But Louis is dead.
You got all his money
and you ran away.
- What are you saying?
That's not. No.
- It's your fault
that Denton is dead.
- Okay.
One night he showed
up on my doorstep,
freaking out.
He was sure someone
was after him.
He gave me the key
to a storage locker
that was full of cash.
Next day. Dead.
He said he got conned
by someone close to him.
Someone who doesn't
like loose ends.
- No more stalling.
Log into your account
and transfer our money.
- Your revenge story
doesn't split too well
between six people now, does it?
- Maybe not, but eight mil will.
- Eight million?
You think if
I had eight million
that I'd be in Gaithersburg?
- I know every penny
Denton had in his account
the day he died.
- And I don't have it.
The storage had
two million cash.
What I offered you
is all I have left.
The rest, I don't know,
maybe someone else took it,
or maybe it burned
up in the fire.
- A fire? What fire?
- Denton died in a
fire in his office.
- Not just Denton.
His staff.
They also burned alive.
It was horrible.
- Hang on a second.
You're saying Denton
got conned by someone
who doesn't leave
loose ends and-
- And he died in a fire.
- Doesn't this
sound like that guy?
- Jovan?
- Did you know Jovan
was involved in this?
- I swear to Christ, if
you got Jess entangled
with that devil, I
will fucking end you.
- All right, all right, easy.
Everybody just relax.
Okay?
- Can someone please
tell me who he is?
- The ultimate sham.
- I hear one time
somewhere in South America,
Jovan talked some guy into
buying the moon for him.
Like, like the actual moon.
- It was South
Africa, Johannesburg.
He burns everything
to the ground.
Anyone who sees his face,
marks and shams alike,
nobody lives to tell the tale.
- And yet the tale
somehow gets told.
Jesus Christ, you
fucking amateurs!
- Amateurs?
So you haven't worked
together before?
- Uh, this is actually
my first time working.
- This is, this is my first job.
- Oh, for Christ.
- Uh, ever.
- 'Cause. Sorry.
- You seem to know a lot
about Denton's business.
- I already told you,
we grew up together.
- It's not like any
of them would know
you're lying about
that though, right?
How do they know
that you're not?
What's his name?
- Uh, it's Jovan.
- Jovan.
How do they know
you are not Jovan?
- You're saying, wait,
what are you saying?
- She ain't saying shit.
She's just stalling.
Because she knows that if
she logs into that account,
we're gonna see that
she has $8 million.
Our $8 million.
- Louis's.
- You're not about to
fuck me on this table
like you did my brother.
Sully.
- Yeah?
- It's time.
- And there was a
great rejoicing.
Let's see.
How about this old bad boy?
You know where we're
going with this, right?
- You all right?
- Motherfucker.
I'm just a little
world weary, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm fucking feeling it.
- Come here.
Here.
Go outside.
Get right, come back
when you're ready.
- Let's go, baby.
- Hey, it ain't that
biker smack you used to.
Be careful with it.
- That's fucking
music to my ears.
- All right.
You two, come with me.
Keep your eyes on her.
- What if she's telling the
truth and it's only 1.5?
- You gonna turn your
nose up to 250 K?
Anyway, get plan B ready.
- Why? What about Sully?
- Hey, boss.
Can I talk to you for a second?
- What's up?
Let's go in here.
All right, lover
boy, spit it out.
- She trusts me, right?
- It's getting
intense in there.
I wasn't prepared for this.
- My dad would say that
experience is the best teacher.
- How's he doing, by the way?
- He asked about you.
- Yeah, I was meaning to visit.
- It's okay.
- But the thing is.
- I know, somebody raises you,
it's hard to see them like that.
It's hard for me too.
- Do you think I have
what it takes to do this?
- Isaac, I don't
know if anyone knows
what it takes to be a sham.
They just do it.
- All right, look.
I know what you think of me.
All right? I get it.
People will always
underestimate me.
They always have.
But I'm more than just a
big dick in a little town.
Just some body for hire.
No, I got smarts.
I got, I got, I got
big city smarts.
- Okay. Okay, all
right, all right.
Everyone has a talent, Robert.
I'm sure you're very talented
in a lot of different ways.
- Thanks.
- But being a sham,
is just not one of 'em.
You're a, you're, you're
a street hustler, man.
Look at you.
I can see you
coming a mile away.
You're too obvious.
- Okay.
But maybe it's so obvious
that she won't
even see it coming.
Right? You know, like a, like
a, like a double negative.
- That's not what that means.
- Look boss,
people like me.
I don't know why, but they do.
- You're right.
You're right.
Use these, but don't fuck it up.
- Not fucking this up.
- All right.
- Hi.
Uh, all right, I- I-
I'm, I'm really sorry
everything went, um...
It was supposed to
be easier.
- You call drugging and
raping someone easy.
- Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, uh...
Nothing
happened, you know?
Uh, I mean, we, we, we
made out a little bit,
and that was
really, really nice.
But no, no, uh,
I didn't give you the
roofies until after,
and you passed out, and I
drove you right here, so.
- And chained me to a table.
- Yeah. Uh.
They, they, they
just want the money.
- They? Aren't you one of them?
- No, I mean, you know,
I- I- I wanted to be prime.
I wanted to be, I don't know.
It's like Avery just brought
me in to be a pretty face.
And that's it.
He works alone.
But I thought I did
a good job, right?
I mean, I did good.
I mean, you believe me.
- What do you want,
a Daytime Emmy?
- I don't know.
When I saw you at the
bar, I, I liked you.
I mean, didn't you like me?
- Yeah, I liked you.
Hey, that guy, Avery...
Whoever he really is...
You can't trust him.
- Look, I- I really don't think
he's that Jovan guy.
- How do you know?
I mean, if you
so much as let me
go to the bathroom,
he'll probably kill you.
- Okay, well, if I can get him
to let us go to the bathroom,
and we both live,
will that put your mind at ease?
- I think so.
And I really, I
really need to go.
- Yeah, no,
no, okay, all right.
Um, just, absolutely, um.
Just,
uh, wait right here.
I mean, you know,
I- I'm, I'm sorry.
I know, you know what I mean.
- Okay.
- How's it going?
- I'm
ready to reach her.
This could really
get her to trust you.
Look, all I need is the
keys to let her out.
Just maybe, maybe the gun
or something so I can.
- You are outta your mind.
- Dude, I- I, boss.
She's gotta pee.
So just the keys.
- Here.
Just keep an eye
on her, all right?
- Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Absolutely.
- And hey, no fuck ups.
- I got it.
You okay?
Hey, you all right?
Oh, shoot.
Here.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
What the fuck?
What the hell are
you doing, man?
Come on, get down.
Fuck, come on.
- Get off of me.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Turn around.
- Fuck, against
the wall, or what?
- I said turn around.
- Okay.
- Open the door.
- All right, all
right, all right.
Fuck it, I can't
believe this shit, man.
I can't fucking believe this.
- Be quiet.
- Dude, I fucked this up so bad.
Boss! Somebody help!
- I told you to be quiet.
- What the fuck is going on?
Hey! Stop right there.
Fuck you think you're going?
- I walk outta here or he dies.
- I'm sorry, man.
She fucking betrayed me.
- I don't give a fuck about him.
Hands up.
I said, "Hands where
I can see 'em."
- Fuck!
Can't believe
you fucking shot me.
- Went in and out. You're fine.
- I'm fucking bleeding, man.
- Let's go.
Keep walking.
Go stitch yourself up.
- I can't even walk, you
fucking dick!
- Put 'em on.
Okay.
- He fucking shot me!
- Now, stay
your ass there.
- Fuck!
- What the
hell happened here?
- Holy fuck.
- Rebecca tried to get away.
- So you shot him?
- Yeah, he'll be fine.
- All evidence to the contrary.
- He needs a hospital.
- No, no way. Too much heat.
- No, I know, but
what should we do?
- Maybe we could
drop him and run.
- Okay, we got an
hour and a half
to get this goddamn thing
done, or this is over.
- But,
but, but he'll die.
- I don't wanna die.
- Then he dies.
- I don't wanna fucking die.
- No way.
- Let's go, let's go!
- Sit the fuck down.
- Hey!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
- Get off me!
- Easy, easy. Easy
- I get, I get this is personal,
but it's not worth it.
- Give me a knife.
- The fuck it isn't.
- Help me.
Please, please.
Will someone please-
- I can't just
stand here while...
- Well, now
help him out Sully.
- I got you, bro.
- Yeah, bro, thank you.
- Here we go.
- Thanks, man.
- Let me just...
- What the fuck?
Woo, woo, woo,
what the fuck man?
What the fuck?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
- I'll get a coffee.
- Stick him
in a holding cell.
Clean this shit up.
- Is he gonna be okay?
- Don't act like you
fucking give a shit.
You used him as a human shield.
- Is that why you shot him?
- No one lives to
tell the story.
- Don't push me.
- So you're gonna pick
them off one-by-one.
Is that your plan?
- Geez. Listen, this
is crazy, all right.
Avery is not Jovan.
- How do you know?
- How do I know about anything?
If I'm looking at a psychopath,
I might as well be
looking at your boyfriend.
- You're suggesting I'm Jovan?
- Look, he's not Jovan.
I'm not Jovan. Nobody's Jovan.
It's fictional. Okay?
- It's not fictional. Avery.
I think my father met him.
I don't know, maybe
10, 15 years ago.
- Well, that doesn't
prove it's not Avery.
- You know what?
- She did not speak her meaning?
- Sully, if she says
one more thing, brother.
- You do to her what you're
gonna do to the rest of us.
- I've had enough of your shit!
- Back off. Back off, man.
What do you, you need to keep me
from my expert doings here?
Come on.
We had an agreement, right?
Five happy minutes.
She'll tell us
all we wanna know,
or we see what her
insides look like.
Boom. Done.
- Go ahead.
- So what's it gonna be?
Truth or dare?
I know, that's the fuzzy part.
You okay?
- Fuck!
- What? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
- What the fuck?
- Help?
What the?
Do something!
I don't know what's wrong?
Help him!
Avery, Sully needs help!
Breathe! Breathe!
Help!
- Sully!
- Breathe, breathe!
Breathe in for me.
Sully! Sully!
- Sully!
- All right,
we're fine, guys.
Everything's going fine.
- Are we fine?
He's dead. Like what
happened in there?
- Doesn't matter.
All right, hold on.
- It matters to
Robert and Sullivan.
- Let me tell you something.
As much shit as this bitch
is putting us through,
I'm gonna make that bitch pay.
- How?
- Jess.
She's just as fucked up
as this motherfucker was.
I don't like to work
bloody, but guess what?
I'll make an exception for her.
Come on, let's put him in
a holding cell with Robert.
- One, two, three.
- You really loved him?
- You know the Pace?
- Like a cult?
- No.
Like the biker gang.
God.
Like, gimme a little smack,
I'd do whatever, right?
One night there
was a poker game.
Sully went all-in
against this Puerto Rican
I was riding with.
All-in meant me too.
Sully won me with
a pair of sixes.
Best night of my life.
He took care of me.
Treat me right.
- You've been promoted.
You up for it?
- Sure.
- Good.
Make it quick.
Unless Rebecca had
a change of heart.
- I can't watch this.
- Yes, you can. Hold her down.
- This is for Sully.
- Ah!
If you ask me,
Avery did you a favor
when he spiked Sully's drugs.
- Get the fuck outta here!
Get her outta here!
- Let me go!
- What the fuck
is wrong with you?
You wanna fuck up our payday?
Get her the fuck outta here!
Jesus Christ.
- She's mad!
- Take the cuffs off.
Move the table.
Just move the table.
Trying to take the
easy way out, huh?
- I was hoping she'd turn on you
since you killed Sully.
- If you had anything
to do with Sully,
I'll fucking kill you!
- Told him it was pure.
- Calm down.
- He just took too much.
- Jess, please.
- You...
- Please calm down.
- Hm.
Everybody out.
Grab your stuff.
We need to talk.
Hello?
- Okay, look.
- How may I direct your call?
- I know that what you must
be going through right now
must be tough.
I liked Sully too.
I think it's only fair
that if you help us finish this,
that you'll get a
piece of his cut too.
Can you do this?
Shh.
Anyone there?
- Hello?
This is Tiffany.
- A little early.
Yeah, yeah. Text me
before you start.
All right.
- What's next?
- We got an hour before
they start demolition.
- Mm-hmm.
- You need to take a
few minutes? Go ahead.
I got another job
for you right now.
You must be pleased
with yourself.
- I didn't want anyone to die.
- Neither did I.
- You don't seem to care.
- Don't lecture me.
Collaterals happen every sham.
- Right.
I mean, I'm not a scam artist,
but I know how to read people.
- Is that how you pulled
the wool over Denton's eyes?
Hmm?
Or is that thing
between your legs
just that fucking special?
- I already
told you I loved him.
- Yeah. And now he's dead.
And you got a shit ton of
money that you didn't earn.
His wife earned it.
I sure as hell earned it.
- Yeah,
when you burned him alive.
- Fuck you!
Look, you can
deflect all you want,
but I promise you I'm
gonna get what I'm after.
So when I found you,
I went into this
little standard recon,
nothing special.
And I found out that
you're leaving town,
which confused me.
I mean, here you are,
all this money you have now.
You got a great friend here.
I mean, look at her.
It's your buddy.
You got a little newborn, right?
It's cute, isn't it?
You guys look, dare
I say, like a family?
It's your baby, right? Yeah.
And I'm like, "We need
to talk to Sarah."
Find out what the
hell's going on here.
And so we did, right?
So we talked to her.
We even had an
agreement, didn't we?
An agreement that when
it was your time to play,
you chose to get cold feet.
Hey, I don't like that shit.
What the fuck is wrong with her?
What is she saying?
You read people, right?
What do you read in her?
- I don't know.
Fear?
It's not like we're close.
- What?
We tried to bribe her.
She said no.
She said she was your friend.
- I guess good friends
still exist, right?
Praise the Lord.
- To get
her to play along,
we had to motivate her properly.
- Someone bumped him.
- Where is he?
- Let's stay
focused on Sarah.
Why?
She's just a lonely
single mother
I drink wine with on occasion.
Just leave her alone, okay?
I barely know her.
Leave her alone.
She's nothing to do with this.
I barely, barely know her.
- We've wasted enough time.
You gonna transfer the
money so she can live?
- I don't have
the eight million.
- There you go. There you go.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's all right.
Well?
- What the fuck? What
the fuck are you doing?
- The fuck are you doing?
- What the fuck is this?
- Are you crazy?
- This is not what I
fucking signed up for.
- Turn it down.
- All right, listen
to me, all right?
It's not what we fucking
thought, all right?
Look at that. Look at Tintin.
Look at this kid.
Look at the skin tone.
Look at the fucking hair.
Sarah adopted this kid.
This is not fucking Sarah's kid.
This is Rebecca's
kid. He's a year old.
Denton died, what,
21 months ago?
Just look at him.
Isn't that right, Rebecca?
A little souvenir from
your time with Denton.
My guess is that she
abandoned Brandon.
- Sorry, I actually, I see
you here every single day.
I'm Sarah.
- Rebecca.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- What? You got
seller's remorse?
- I totally assumed
that you were
a mom watching her kid here.
- No, I- I don't have kids.
- Is that why you're
back, befriending Sarah?
Checking in on your baby.
- I- I just adopted him,
so it's in the process.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
So we're kind of new
to each other as well.
- Yeah.
Well, he's beautiful.
- I mean, why else
would she be back
in this town of all places?
- What's his name?
- His name's Brandon.
- Brandon. Hi, Brandon.
- Brandon, did you
make a friend at the park?
- It's okay.
- It's pathetic.
Come on, I got you.
Okay, here we go.
Come on, it's okay.
It's okay.
- Almost.
- Okay.
Okay, just stay here.
We're almost done.
- It's okay.
- Good catch in there
with the baby, Moon.
Your dad would be proud.
- Thank you, um.
- But.
- Oops.
That was the second
time you questioned me
in front of someone.
Don't let there
be a third, okay?
- Mm.
- Good.
Let's see what we got here.
Look at you.
Whoosh-up little man.
- You're not gonna hurt him?
He's just a little baby.
- What did we just say?
Listen, I'm not gonna
do anything to this kid
that she doesn't force me to do.
You understand me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Whoosh-up little man.
- Hi.
- It's cool.
- There you go.
- You need this to happen
more than anybody
else in here, okay?
Your father's chemo ain't cheap.
Remember that?
I hired you to be
a professional.
So act like one, please.
Look, all you have to do
is just follow my
lead, that's it.
Don't question anything.
Don't get in your head, don't.
Just follow what I do
and we'll be out
of this in no time.
Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right?
- Okay.
Come here.
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
It's okay, it's all right.
Yes. Mm-hmm, mm.
All right. Okay, little man.
Almost there.
You're gonna help
us get our money.
Yes, you are. Yes you are.
He's cute.
- Just stay quiet, please. Okay?
Okay. Just, just relax!
Okay? Just stay quiet.
- He's killing us.
Just like she said.
Sully told me all about Jovan.
He and his partner went into
the Chicago diamond district
with a pocket full
of broken glass,
walked out with half a mil.
Partner got greedy,
put a bullet in Jovan
and hit the road.
Jovan killed him,
killed his wife,
killed his whole family,
killed his parrot.
His fucking parrot.
No fire, but still
everyone knows it was him.
- Okay, what, what
are you talking about?
So what?
- So if there's even a chance
that Avery could be him,
we got to move on him
first, or we're both dead!
- Okay, you're sure about this?
- If you're too much of a
pussy, just gimme the gun.
Otherwise go take-
- You know,
Denton was
the closest thing
to family I ever had.
When I lost him,
when he was murdered,
a piece of me was murdered too.
Looking into this baby's eyes,
I see him.
I see Denton,
and I'm his uncle,
and, and I feel like
I got family again.
Do you think maybe,
since you don't wanna
give the money up,
you think maybe I could just,
just keep the baby instead?
Please.
No?
Fuck it!
- What do you want?
What do you want?
- Doesn't feel good, does it?
We can do
this all fucking day.
Or we can end this now.
You decide.
- Yes.
- Moon!
There he is.
Come to Uncle Avery.
That's right. Yes.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
That's right. It's okay.
She'll be fine. She's okay.
- Please.
- Good boy.
That's right.
Reunited. Like a family.
I'll be outside.
Good boy. That's right.
- No. No, please.
- Was I right?
Is that why you stayed?
- Yes.
- That was brilliant.
- I only do what
she makes me do.
I'll tell you what,
this bitch keeps fucking around,
it'll be the real baby.
But I think we got her
where we want her, so.
What's up kid?
You do what I asked you to do?
Hello?
Good.
Look at you turning into a sham.
All right, we gotta hurry up.
This thing's almost
over. Come on, let's go.
Moon, grab the laptop,
leave the baby.
- Let's go!
- You know what to do.
- What happens after
I transfer the money?
- You know what happens.
Denton's blood is on your hands,
but I'll make it quick
and I'll spare the
life of the baby.
- And do what with him?
- I kind of like the idea
of raising him on my own.
It's poetic.
- It's child abuse
is what it is.
- And he'd be
better off with you?
Come on, let's go! Log in.
Come on!
- Where's the girl?
- Oh my God. Jess is fine, okay?
Let's go, log in.
She told me to.
- Isaac?
- She, she told me.
- What's going on?
- It was
an accident, okay?
I- I- I- I- I didn't
expect her to fall, okay?
- You had him kill Jess?
- I didn't have him do shit!
I just told him to
keep her outta my way.
That's it.
- You killed her?
- I'm, I'm done.
Okay? I'm done
with this bullshit.
I'm taking the baby.
- Only way you're
taking that baby
is in a body bag, motherfucker.
- No kidding.
I am not letting you take him.
- Isaac.
You know that I need
this money for my father.
- Not like this.
- It doesn't work
without the baby.
- He wouldn't have wanted
you to hurt someone.
- I don't have a choice.
- Well, I do!
- Don't make me do this.
Don't make me ruin you.
Put the gun down.
- I can't.
- Isaac, you're not a killer.
What happened with
Jess was an accident.
I know this.
Matter of fact,
I know you weren't gonna
bring any harm to her,
which is why the
gun that I gave you,
has only got blanks in it, man.
- What? You're lying.
- Isaac, look at me.
I'm putting the gun down.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- I never should have let
you talk me into this.
- You're right.
I should have never brought
you in, it's my fault.
I'm sorry for all of us.
Please put the gun down.
Just put it down.
Please. I'm sorry.
Okay.
Don't move.
We both know that this
is the gun that's loaded.
Does that offer still stand?
- It still stands.
- Money first.
- You know,
you should've just
done the smart thing.
Taken your money,
left the kid and just gone away.
- I wanted to make
sure he was safe.
I didn't know how hard
it'd be to say goodbye.
- Nobody's perfect.
- Obviously.
Thank God for the pills.
- What pills?
- My pills.
- We took your pills.
- Coffee breath.
Plus track marks. Sedatives.
And the heroin.
After he shot up,
overdose was only
a matter of time.
- Sully's coffee.
Robert too?
- That took some work.
You played your part though.
I helped him bleed out.
Femoral artery.
- I'm
fucking bleeding, man.
- There's no way you
woulda known Isaac woulda...
- Hm, that was a
bit of a Hail Mary.
- Hey, little guy,
you're so cute.
- Will you knock it
off with the baby, kid?
Jesus Christ.
Get into your lawyer shit.
- Hey.
- Not exactly the
infanticidal type.
I told you I know
how to read people.
It's been fun though,
right?
- You fucking bitch!
No! No!
- Hi.
Let's go home.
- Rebecca! Oh my
God, you're alive.
Oh shit.
We're safe, oh my God.
Oh, is Brandon okay?
- He's okay.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hey, he's fine.
- Okay.
- Oh my God.
- We're okay.
Hi, baby. Hi.
What's happening?
Are you his mother?
- I'll explain later.
- And the money, they
said that you stole?
- We should go.
- Oh my God.
- Now!
- Hey, baby.
- I'll take him.
- I called the police.
I told them what
they did to you.
I told them everything.
Rebecca, come on.
- Sarah.
Thank you,
for everything you've
done for Brandon,
and everything
you've done for me.
- Of course.
- Please don't do this to me.
Don't do it, Rebecca.
You got the money.
You got the kid.
Please. Lemme, just lemme live.
Please. Rebecca, please!
Rebecca, please!
- Not my name.
- Jovan? Jovan!
Jovan!
- How may
I direct your call?
- It's Jovan.
Yes, the same method as before.
Everything burned down,
nothing left for us.
That's right.
Seven bodies.
Sir, yeah, no, I
understand, sir,
but we got here as
soon as we could.
- Yes, sir.
I hate to say it, but he
could be anywhere by now.
- No, I-
No, we're not really
sure how he worked.
No. Not entirely clear
at the motive either.
- Yeah, there's not
a doubt in my mind.
It's him.
- On my way.